Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
=Vengeful Wife=
=Episode 20=
Master,
breaking news.
Ye Dong took Bai Cha away and settled
her in the old house of Lin family.
After Lin Xia's incident,
Ye Dong moved out soon.
This time, he actually put
his new lover
in his ex-wife's home.
This is unexpected.
She might not be a new lover.
According to inside sources of Jiuyao,
Ye Dong will reveal
the candidate for CEO
at press briefing tomorrow.
Is he seriously making Bai Cha
the CEO of Jiuyao Group?
Bai Cha?
Mom.
Mom. Why are you still awake so late?
Mom,
what's wrong?
Mom.
Still remember I'm your mother?
No,
you're my mother.
I should honor you.
I should worry about you.
Mom,
why are you saying these?
Are you a demon?
Today, Bai Cha
was taken by someone
named Ye Dong.
I can see
something is on her mind.
She looked distressed and sad.
She said everyone around her is a demon.
Doesn't that mean you?
Be honest with me.
What outrageous things have you done?
You...
You won't say, huh?
You brat,
just admit it.
Mom,
what are you doing?
Cheng Nuo,
no matter what you've done,
be honest
and explain it to me.
Make amends where it's needed,
and make up for what's lost.
If you are wrong,
you must admit it.
I believe
you're not an irredeemable person.
Mom,
please don't worry.
If I don't, who will?
Bai Cha has no parents.
As her mother-in-law,
I'm her guardian.
Want me to stay out of it?
Unless you stop being my son.
She got pregnant for you
and had a miscarriage,
yet you betrayed her.
Last night, you didn't come home.
Are you...
You,
you!
Mom.
You brat,
admit it.
Mom.
Admit it.
Admit you're wrong!
Mom,
I wronged Bai Cha.
I wronged our child.
Cheng Nuo,
no matter what you've done,
I have only one request.
Now,
make amends with her
and bring her back.
Mom,
Bai Cha
will never come back.
The real Bai Cha
was dead
when she
fell off the cliff.
She's dead?
Don't talk nonsense!
That's...
That is
Lin Xia.
What Lin Xia?
How is this possible?
But she clearly is...
Mom.
Mom,
listen to me.
Lin Xia
hates Ye Dong so much.
She assumed Bai Cha's identity
to start anew
and reclaim what belongs to her.
What a pitiful girl!
And my poor daughter-in-law,
Bai Cha.
Both are victims of demon Ye Dong.
Cheng Nuo.
Let's call the police now.
Have that demon arrested.
Mom,
I have my own plans.
I kept it from you
for your own safety.
Cheng Nuo.
I understand your difficulties.
I won't interfere.
But
promise me one thing.
Tell me,
Mom.
Protect yourselves,
especially Lin Xia.
She's suffered enough in this life.
I understand.
(From now on,)
(you are no longer Lin Xia.)
(You are Bai Cha.)
(All of this)
(is Ye Dong's fault.)
(Ye Dong,)
(I will reclaim everything)
(I've lost.)
You saved me.
Everyone thinks
Bai Cha
was merely injured.
But she died
when she fell off the cliff.
It's Ye Dong's fault.
I imagine you hate Ye Dong
no less than I do.
I want him to face proper judgment.
I'll reclaim what's rightfully mine.
I can help you,
but I have one condition.
What is it?
I can help you reclaim
everything you've lost,
but you must promise me
to follow my plan exactly.
What plan?
Now that your face is disfigured
and you're wanted everywhere,
you should
assume Bai Cha's identity
and return to Ye Dong.
Have you been monitoring him all along?
Yes.
Then my father's death...
Your father...
I discovered his death
when I tracked them dumping the body.
At that time,
I tried to save you,
but failed.
Lin Na's death
was also an accident.
Why didn't you call the police earlier?
If you called the police,
Na wouldn't have died.
I considered doing so,
but do you know
Man City has no death penalty?
I want that bad guy
to pay for his crimes
with his life.
Hello.
Why didn't you pick up earlier?
Miss me so much
that you fell asleep?
Guess.
I just finished the group meeting.
Everything's arranged.
Your appointment as CEO tomorrow
is a done deal.
I'm coming to celebrate
with you now.
If you come,
I'll leave.
Hang up.
Bai Cha,
you're becoming more fascinating.
Playing hard to get
makes me crave you more.
Dong,
women understand women best.
The more you flatter her,
the more arrogant she becomes.
Exactly.
The one I carve for eludes me.
The one I push away still stays.
Just like you.
I won't
leave even if driven away.
I'll stick to you.
You're wearing new perfume.
This scent
is so alluring.
Right.
I'll dress up for those who love me.
Dong,
love me.
(Cheng Nuo made the perfume for you.)
(Enjoy it.)
♪Like a forgotten flower♪
♪Silently scattered across the horizon♪
♪Bathed in silent starlight♪
♪One day it will bloom♪
♪Let time heal the wounds♪
♪Clench the trembling hands♪
♪Embrace the faith of rebirth♪
♪The ending won't come too late♪
♪Under the mask♪
♪Observing all truths and lies♪
♪Who can see my strength♪
♪Tears soak my face♪
♪Under the mask♪
♪Seeking light in the darkness♪
♪What couldn't be let go♪
♪Eventually turns to dust in the wind♪
♪Under the mask♪
♪Observing all truths and lies♪
♪Who can see my strength♪
♪Tears soak my face♪
♪Under the mask♪
♪Seeking light in the darkness♪
♪What couldn't be let go♪
♪Eventually turns to dust in the wind♪